你是上帝的军队统帅
- 安东尼奥 - 所以是真的吗
- Antonio! - And is it true?
我诱发了一个男孩的心脏病 杀了他
That I killed a boy by provoking a heart attack?
驱魔师 见鬼
An exorcist. For fuck's sake.
他们把他从罗马赶来这里
They throw him out of Rome and send him here to us.
对 把他发配到这个偏僻小镇
That's right. To the ass end of the world.
他们要来了
They're coming for you.
他们在找到它之前都不会停下的
They're not going to stop until they find it.
他们在找什么
What are they looking for?
如果你喜欢可以留着 只是一块金属而已
You can keep it if you like. It's just a piece of metal.
我也不知道为什么留着它 它一文不值
I don't even know why I kept it. It's worthless.
这个镇子安静祥和 什么都没发生过
This is a peaceful place. Nothing happens here.
你突然来了 麻烦也接踵而至
Suddenly you arrive and all hell breaks loose.
想要恐吓我的人
Someone who wants to scare me.
HBO 欧洲出品
深影字幕组倾情奉献
HBO-拉丁美洲参与制作
不好意思
主教阁下
我知道
我们要除掉他吗
我们需要他活着
现在他很困惑
虽然他不是他们的人 但也不是我们的人
我不想从他手里抢
要让他主动给我
佩德拉萨谋杀案
突发精神异常的女士杀害了自己的丈夫并从救护车中逃脱
警察最终在镇教堂将其逮捕
- 没有提到那个婴儿吗 - 半真半假
- And it doesn't mention the baby? - They make half of it up.
他们说它可能
They say it could have
被偷了 埋在了井里
been stolen and that it's buried in a well.
你什么时候去见拉古纳
What time are you seeing Laguna?
- 半小时后 - 你准备怎么说
- In half an hour. - What are you going to tell him?
埃莱娜 没有人会相信的
Elena, no one is going to believe it.
最后会变成我们对抗...
In the end it's our word against...
- 对抗什么 - 常识
- Against what? - Against common sense.
我们都看见了 不是吗
We both saw it, didn't we?
我们遇见的事是这样的
What happened to us was this,
我们处于极度紧张的情况下...
that in a moment of nervous crisis...
我不是紧张 是害怕
I wasn't nervous! I was terrified.
这证实了我的观点
That proves my point.
你的大脑利用了你脑海中的图像
The mind uses those images that you have in your head
把它们投影在了你眼前
and projects them in front of you.
对普通人来说 这就是梦境
It happens to normal people when they dream,
我们只是醒着的时候经历了这些
but in cases like ours, it happens when we're awake.
你说的是幻觉
That's called a hallucination.
难道我们产生了同样的幻觉吗
Did we both have the same hallucination?
不可能吗 我们当时都在屋里看见了毛网
Why not? We were both in the house and we saw the wool webs.
- 埃莱娜 - 你和贝尔加拉神父谈过了
- Elena... - You've been talking to Fr. Vergara.
如果这都是他的错呢
And what if it's all his fault?
不要再讨论这件事了 好吗
Let's not go back to that, please.
卡门说他从他们那儿偷了些什么
Carmen said that he had stolen something from them,
他有他们想要的东西
that he has something they wanted.
她在家里也说过这话 确实如此
She said that in the house too, that's true.
他们在找的是这个
Well, they were looking for this.
一枚银币 看起来很旧
A coin? It looks old.
没有人问过为什么他在教堂藏了座兵工厂吗
Has no one asked him why he has an arsenal hidden in the church?
帕科 他在说谎
Paco, he's lying to us.
他伪装成无神论者
He pretends he's a skeptic
但对这个东西的信仰远超于我们
but believes in this much more than we do.
他有暴力倾向 但同时也十分聪明
He's violent, but he also seems very intelligent.
把银币还给我
Give me back the coin.
30枚银币
第一季  第二集
导 演
亚历克斯·德·拉·伊格莱西亚
就是这个 对
It's that one, yes.
看到了吗 检查一下
See? Check it out.
- 对 就是这只脚 - 你确定吗
- Yes, it's this leg. - Are you sure?
对 这只脚受力时 他会抬头来减轻负重
Yes. When he leans on it, he raises his head to ease the weight.
他这里受伤了 但还算及时
He's got an injury here. But we're still in time.
再晚几个月 我们就无能为力了
In a couple of months, we wouldn't be able to do anything.
没有你我该怎么办啊
I'd be lost without you.
要喝点什么吗
Would you like a drink?
我要去换衣服
While I go get changed.
这边
This way.
这是怎么弄得
How did you get that?
我才发现 你的脸怎么了
I've just noticed. What's happened to your face?
把猫抓进笼子可不容易
Putting cats into their cages is no easy job.
不如你来和我一起吧
Why don't you come with me?
- 什么 - 我是说工作
- Excuse me? - Professionally, I mean.
你在诊所能挣多少
How much do you earn at the clinic?
不重要 我付你双倍
It doesn't matter. I'll pay you double.
三倍
Triple?
别胡说了
Don't talk nonsense.
你付我的已经很多了
Anyway, you already pay me too much.
赛马季还有一个月就开始了
The season is starting in a month.
你难道不想周游世界吗
Wouldn't you like to travel the world?
我们会共度良辰 辗转于比赛
We'd have a great time, going from race to race.
那谁照顾奶牛和猪呢
And who'd look after the cows and pigs?
埃莱娜 谁都可以
Jesus, Elena, anyone.
你有天赋 而你应该物尽其用
What you have is a gift, and you have to make the most of it.
你真的要卖掉城堡吗
Is it true you're going to sell the castle?
城堡的维护就像在撒钱
Maintaining this place is just throwing money away.
还有 你的朋友 镇长...
Also, your friend, the mayor...
- 帕科 - 对 帕科
- Paco? - Yes, Paco.
他在税收上制约我
He's crippling me with taxes.
他在竞选中赢了你 你还在耿耿于怀
You still haven't forgiven him for beating you in that election.
恰恰相反 他帮了我
On the contrary, he did me a favor.
真不知道我当时为什么要参选
I don't know why on earth I ran for mayor.
赢了就会像他一样 要为所有人排忧
Now I'd be like him, having to listen to everyone's complaints.
但落选后 两小时后我就能到马德里
But instead, I can get in the car and be in Madrid in two hours,
在任何地方享用晚餐
to have dinner wherever I want.
我知道一家米其林餐厅 两星...
I know a place that has two Michelin stars...
- 不了 - 好吧
- The answer's no. - Alright.
那在这儿喝杯咖啡怎么样 在城镇广场
What about a coffee right here, in the town square?
谢了 贝尔纳达 再见
Thanks, Bernarda. See you.
能在这儿见到你太好了 大人
It's great to see you here, my lord!
不 罗赫略 那是我父亲
No, Rogelio, that was my father.
我只是罗克 对谁都一样
I'm just Roque, for everyone.
两杯咖啡 伊莎贝尔 一杯加糖
Two coffees, Isabel. One with saccharin.
- 马上就好 - 恩里克 最近好吗
- Coming. - Hi, Enrique. How are you?
- 你好 - 埃莱娜
- How are you? - Hi, Elena.
现在能告诉我你怎么了吗
And now will you tell me what's wrong with you?
- 你看起来很冷漠 - 我只是累了
- You seem distant. - I'm just tired.
我的工作太多了 仅此而已
I've had a lot of work, that's all.
你不想告诉我
So you're not going to tell me.
- 我以为我们是朋友 - 对 我不会说的
- I thought we were friends. - No, I'm not going to tell you.
为什么
Why not?
帕科
Paco!
罗克 埃莱娜
Hey, Roque. Hello, Elena.
- 帕科 - 一杯咖啡
- Hello, Paco. - A coffee, please.
给镇长来杯咖啡
Get the mayor a coffee.
所以 公务缠身
So? A lot of work?
我不能抱怨
I can't complain.
有一段时间没见到你了
We haven't seen you around here for a while.
最近一直在赛马
I've been racing around so
脑袋都被时差搞晕了
much my head's spinning with all the jet leg.
- 被什么 - 时差
- With what? - The time change.
- 就是跨洋的时候 - 什么羊
- When you across the pond. - What pond?
你太夸张了
You're too much.
总之 一切都还一如既往 对吗
But anyway, I see that everything's pretty much the same, right?
你可能不信 我们最近非常...忙
Don't you believe it. We've been very... busy recently.
帕科和梅尔切新开了一家屠宰场
Paco and Merche have opened a new abattoir.
我知道
I know.
我都听说了 这件事和其他的事
I hear about everything. About that and other things.
我有些可靠的消息来源
I've got good informers.
不好意思 什么
Excuse me. Yes?
当然 多少钱
Sure. How much is it?
那买下来
Buy it then.
你怎么样
How are you doing?
还不错
Fine.
- 很多工作 - 那挺好的
- Working a lot. - That's good.
- 我... 我得走了 - 你的咖啡还没喝
- I've been... Well, I have to go. - You haven't had your coffee.
对 我只是...
Sure, I just...
记得要买下来 一会儿再说
But don't forget to buy it. Talk later.
不好意思
Sorry.
一群废物 什么事都得我亲自操办
That lot are useless. I have to do everything.
帕科呢 他怎么走了
And Paco? Why did he leave?
你到底去哪儿了
Where the hell were you?
- 附近 - 附近
- Around. - Around?
- 把外面的桌子擦了 - 她可以做
- Clear the tables outside. - She can do it.
不要顶撞我
Don't talk back to me,
不要碰煎蛋卷 那是给客人准备的
and don't eat the omelet, it's for the customers!
所有事情都得我自己做
I have to do it all by myself.
- 你在干什么 - 怎么了
- What the fuck are you doing? - What?
如果被你爸发现
If your father catches you...
你不告诉他 他就不会发现
If you don't tell him anything, he won't find out.
小子 再动手动脚 我就扇你
Hey, kid, do that again and I'll slap your face!
一个辣妹出现了...
Now one of those hot girls shows up...
拿到冰块了吗
Have you got ice?
怎么样 小子
How are you, kid?
这就吓坏了吗 害怕了
You're shitting yourselves already? You're scared.
- 已经害怕了吗 - 嗯
- Scared already? - Yes.
- 我们真的要做吗 - 来吧
- So, are we going to do it, or what? - Yes, right?
你们是认真的吗
Are you guys serious?
- 我浑身起鸡皮疙瘩 - 别扫兴
- It gives me the creeps. - Don't be such a drag.
最胆小的人呈什么能呢
When the biggest coward acts all brave...
她说得对 我们来不就是为了这个吗
She's right. That's why we're here, isn't it?
我去 你用过显灵镜吗
Fuck, have you used the Ouija glass?
黏糊糊的 哪头猪用的
It's all sticky. Who was the pig?
真恶心
Gross!
把手指放在上面 别用力 好吗
Put your fingers on the edge. And don't push, okay?
太恶心了
That's so gross.
你们在干嘛 刚刚是怎么回事
What are you doing? What is this?
你们都推它了 别动它
You're all moving it. Stop it.
如果我们这样胡闹 我就走了
If we're going to start messing around, I'm leaving.
我什么都没做
I'm not doing anything.
我们还没开始提问 它就动了
We haven't even started asking questions and it's moving already!
我觉得是你妈妈
I bet it's your mother.
你什么意思 别提我妈妈
What do you mean? Leave my mother alone.
你妈妈去世多久了
How long is it since your mother died?
- 三个月 - 所以呢
- Three months? - And?
她肯定很想跟你说话
Well, I bet she really wants to talk to you.
- 为什么她想跟我说话 - 因为她自杀了
- Why would she want to talk to me? - Because she killed herself.
该死
Shit...
- 我要走了 - 别 放松点
- I'm leaving. - Come on, ease up.
也许不是你妈妈 但我们身边有鬼魂
Maybe it isn't your mother, but one of these around us.
问问他们的名字
Ask what their name is.
你叫什么名字
What's your name?
希... 亚...
G... i... a...
希亚...
Gia...
希亚科...
Giaco...
希亚科莫
Giacomo.
- 希亚科莫 - 见鬼 他是意大利人
- Giacomo... - Shit, he's Italian.
看吧 不是她
See? It isn't her.
你是哪里人 希亚科莫
Where are you from, Giacomo?
加埃塔
Gaeta.
- 加埃塔 - 滚吧
- Gaeta? - Go eat some excreta.
闭嘴 白痴
Shut up, dickhead.
你们真的没动它吗
Are you really not moving it?
- 没有 我们没有 - 没有
- No, we're not. - No.
问他是不是死了
Ask him if he's dead.
我为什么要问他这个 白痴
Why would I ask him that, moron?
见鬼 他死了
Shit... He's dead.
- 你在天堂还是地狱 -你不能这么问
- Are you in heaven or hell? - You don't fucking ask like that.
你得先问一件事 然后再问另一件
First you ask one thing, and then the other.
我...
I am...
在...
H...
这里
...ere.
- 见鬼 - 见鬼
- Fuck! - For fuck's sake!
- 谁碰了我 - 去你们的
- Who touched me? - You can all go fuck yourselves!
- 不要摸我 - 都打开手机电筒 蠢货
- Hey, no groping! - The torch on your phones, dummies.
我没电了
I have no battery.
该死 吓死我了
Fuck, I was really scared.
有人吸我的耳朵
Someone sucked my ear.
- 这不好玩... - 不是我干的
- It's not funny... - It wasn't me.
- 你这头猪 - 我发誓不是我
- You're such a pig. - It wasn't me, I swear!
索莱呢
Where's Sole?
- 真是个贱人 - 索莱
- What a bitch. - Sole!
索莱
Sole!
一点都不好玩 你到底在哪
It ain't fucking funny! Where the fuck are you?
见鬼 索莱
Fuck! Sole!
索莱 拜托 快出来
Sole, for fuck's sake, come on!
索莱 见鬼
Sole, fuck!
- 索莱 - 索莱
- Sole! - Sole!
叫救护车了吗
Have you called the hospitals?
那就现在叫
Well, start doing it.
我拿来了这个
I've brought this.
很好
Good.
谢谢你 马丁
Thank you, Martín.
别担心
Don't worry.
闻闻
Sniff.
去左边 去左边
To the left. Go to the left.
这边
This way.
四周都找找
Look around there.
看看墓碑后面
Behind the gravestone.
- 镇长 - 该死
- Mayor. - Fuck...
那些瓶子是我酒吧的
Those bottles come from my bar.
你好 里奇 过来
Hello, Richi. Come here.
别怕 没事的
You needn't be scared, it's all right.
不用害怕 我要打死他
He needn't be scared? I'm going to beat the shit out of him.
- 冷静 冷静 - 我怎么跟你说的
- Relax! Relax! - What did I tell you?
- 恩里克 拜托 - 坐下
- Enrique, please. - Sit down.
他从酒吧偷酒 孔查
He took the bottles from the bar, Concha.
你儿子是个骗子
Your son's a crook!
这也不是第一次了 我一直盯着他呢
And it isn't the first time. I've had my eye on him.
听着 里奇 今天你们都要
Look, Richi, today you'll all
去给警官录口供
have to go give a statement to the sergeant.
但在那之前
But before that, we still
你有机会先告诉我们真相
have a chance for you to tell us the truth.
他什么都不知道 他已经告诉我了
The boy knows nothing, he told me already.
里卡多 如果你们之间发生了什么
Let's see, Ricardo, if anything happened between you,
如果发生了你们无法预料
if there was an accident, something that no one wanted to happen,
无法控制的意外 最好现在告诉我们
but that got out of your control, it's best if you tell us now
因为最终一切都会水落石出
because it's all going to come out in the end.
真的什么都没发生 她突然就不见了
But nothing happened, really. Suddenly she wasn't there.
就是这样 蜡烛熄灭了
That's how it was. The candles blew out
我们打开灯后 她就不在了
and when we looked again, she wasn't there!
里卡多 你在说什么胡话
Ricardo, what you're saying doesn't make sense.
没人会因为玩笔仙消失
No one disappears from playing with the Ouija.
玩这个游戏非常危险 真是胡闹
Playing with it is very dangerous nonsense
因为人们一旦害怕 事情都会变得很糟
because people get scared and things can end badly.
- 尤其是喝醉的时候 - 没错 我这么说
- Especially if you were drinking! - Exactly. And in saying that
就是我认为
I'm making it clear that
你们有事瞒着我们
something happened that you're not telling us.
- 我猜他们在抽大麻 - 闭嘴 孔查
- I bet they were smoking joints. - Be quiet, Concha.
我们找到了这些毒品
We found these pills.
- 是你的吗 我打死你 - 别激动 住手
- Are they yours? I'll kill you! - Take it easy. Stop!
- 冷静点 - 什么
- Stay calm! - What?
看看你都干了什么
Look what you've done.
哭吧 你摊上大麻烦了
Go on, you're right to cry, you're in big trouble.
毫无收获 没有任何可疑的迹象
Nothing. Not a single trace of anything suspicious.
- 然后呢 - 我没有线索 帕科
- Well, then? - I have no clue, Paco.
要么是她自己想离开
Either she left because she
要么是他们把她带走了
wanted to or they took her away between all of them.
但如果有任何暴力行为 一定会留下痕迹
But if there had been any violence, we'd have seen signs of it,
现场或孩子们身上 肯定有痕迹
either at the site, or on the kids.
我们逐个检查了他们
We examined them one by one,
没有任何挣扎打斗的痕迹
and there wasn't a single sign of a fight or even a struggle.
出什么事了
What's happened?
库罗都告诉我了 但我不太明白
Curro told me something, but I didn't really understand.
孩子们昨晚出去喝酒了 然后索莱失踪了
The kids went out drinking last night, and Sole hasn't appeared.
- 索莱是谁 - 马丁的女儿
- Sole? Sole who? - Martín's daughter.
-马丁 - 你的警卫
- Martín? - Your guard.
如果你需要我帮忙...
If you need me for anything...
我认识内政部的人
I know people in the Ministry of the Interior.
所以呢
And...?
如果有什么需要做的 告诉我
No, well, if anything has to be done, it'll be done.
我能叫人来帮忙
Call anyone to come and lend a hand...
不用 罗克 谢谢
It's all right, Roque, thanks.
做得不错
Good service.
- 得了吧 - "做得不错" 他是警察吗
- Come on... - "Good service"? Is he a cop now?
你看到和他在一起的是谁了吗
Did you see who was with him?
真可怜
Poor man.
先是他妻子 现在是他女儿
First his wife, and now his daughter.
他们跟了我二十年
They were with me for 20 years.
她是厨师 他是警卫
She was the cook, and he was the guard.
现在他身兼两职了
But he's doing it all now.
她怎么了 是癌症吗
What was it? Cancer?
对 非常常见的一种癌症
Yes, one of those that's diagnosed from one day to the next.
- 她实在无法忍受了 - 太可怕了
- She couldn't bear it. - That's so awful.
爬到那里 一跃而下
She went up there and jumped off.
最糟糕的是 她女儿就在那里
The worst thing is that her daughter was here.
她看着母亲跳下去的
She saw her jump?
请进
Go in.
你好 马丁
Hi, Martín.
我直说了...
Okay, now...
你跟她的朋友们谈过了吗
Have you talked to her friends?
跟埃尔薇拉谈过了
To Elvirita.
- 她说什么 - 跟其他人说的一样
- And what did she say? - What all of them are saying.
突然之间 她就消失了
That suddenly, she wasn't there.
她肯定还说了些别的
But she must have told you something else.
- 说当时有一个鬼魂 - 一个什么
- That a spirit appeared to them. - A what?
一个鬼魂 他们正在
A spirit. They were playing
用玻璃杯玩电影里的那种游戏
that thing with the glass, like in the films.
- 笔仙 - 没错
- A Ouija. - That's it.
然后突然有个意大利鬼魂现身了
And suddenly an Italian spirit appeared to them.
- 意大利鬼魂 - 没错
- Italian? - Yes.
他们为什么要说这种话呢
Why would they say something like that?
我猜是随口编的谎话
I think that if you're going to make something up,
想到什么就说了
you say the first thing you think of,
什么恶魔现身 等等之类的
that the devil appeared, or whatever,
可是名叫希亚科莫的意大利人...
but an Italian called Giacomo...
你是说希亚科莫吗
Did you say Giacomo?
埃尔薇拉 有人要跟你谈谈 埃尔薇拉
Elvira! They want to talk to you! Elvira?
她从昨天开始就这样了
She's been like this since yesterday.
我知道你不想听我说话
I know you're not listening to me.
但是没关系 我会告诉你我的感受
But I don't care, I'll tell you what I feel.
我第一次玩笔仙的时候
When I did the Ouija for the first time,
我们请来了一个叫丘基的鬼魂
we got a ghost called Chuqui.
他一直胡说八道 半个小时后我们腻了
He was talking such rubbish that after half an hour we got bored
就去喝酒了
and went drinking instead.
第二天 我们又试了一次
The next day, we tried again,
丘基又出现了
and Chuqui came up again.
我们都笑了 谁也没把当真...
We started laughing, no one was taking it seriously...
直到后来...
Until suddenly...
丘基说安帕罗跟他在一起
Chuqui said that "Amparo" Was with him
而且安帕罗过得挺好
and that she was all right.
安帕罗是我的祖母
Amparo was my grandmother,
我的朋友们都不知道她的名字
and none of my friends knew that was her name.
你问了她什么
What did you ask her?
我问她是不是在天堂
I asked her if she was in heaven.
她是怎么说的
And what did she say?
她没在天堂
That she wasn't.
她在地狱吗
Was she in hell?
也不在
No.
然后呢
Well then?
她说她在"混沌"之中
She said that she was in the "Fog".
真的吗  "混沌"之中
Seriously? In the fog?
也许我们曲解了她的意思
Maybe we didn't understand her properly.
你相信这些东西吗
Do you believe in those things?
相信
Yes.
我再也没玩过
I never did it again,
但是这件事 至今历历在目
but I remember every word of that Ouija as if it were yesterday.
希亚科莫还说了什么
What else did Giacomo say?
埃莱娜...
Elena...
有多久了了...一个月吗
How long has it been... A month?
一个月没听到你的消息了
A month without hearing from you.
我能理解 回来对你来说不容易
I understand that it's been hard for you to come back.
我想现在 置身事外之后...
I suppose that now, seeing things with more distance...
我们所经历的那种极端暴力的情况
Situations of extreme violence, like the one we experienced,
会摧毁你的神经 很难保持冷静
destroy your nerves. It's hard to keep a steady head,
但是你很坚强 展示出了强大的自制力
but you're strong and you've shown great self-possession.
他叫希亚科莫
He was called Giacomo.
他来自加埃塔 罗马附近的一个小镇
And he was from Gaeta, a town near Rome.
我在谷歌上查过了
I looked him up on Google,
你的希亚科莫 死于驱魔仪式的那个男孩子
and your Giacomo, the boy who died during the exorcism,
就来自于加埃塔 所以少跟我鬼扯
was from Gaeta. So don't give me this shit.
你对我的执着
I'm starting to get worried
让我开始担心了
about this obsession you have with me.
奇怪的是 世界上鬼魂那么多
It's curious that, out of all the spirits in the world,
这五个孩子却偏偏
those five kids chose to
招来了一个来自加埃塔的希亚科莫
call up Giacomo from Gaeta, for their séance.
你又有什么想法
What's your new theory?
我和那个女孩的失踪
I had something to do with
有什么关系吗 是我绑架了她
that girl's disappearance? That I abducted her?
不 我觉得没人绑架她
No, I don't think anyone abducted her.
她失踪了 没错
She disappeared, yes,
但她人在某处 而你会告诉我 她在哪
but she's somewhere, and you're going to tell me where.
听着 埃莱娜 如果你这么肯定
Look, Elena, if you're so convinced
我和整件事情有关
that I've got something to do with all this,
去跟警察说吧
tell the police.
失踪
大家好
Hello. Hello.
非常感谢大家能在
Thank you very much for being
圣多明哥酒店
这么重要的日子莅临
here today at such an important day for us.
我想时机已到
Well, I think the time has arrived.
- 帕科 - 亲爱的...
- Paco? - Darling...
- 快点 帕科 - 不...
- Please, Paco. - No...
- 我的胳膊... - 帕科...
- My arm... - Paco...
宫廷&美味
- 太棒了 - 请说几句吧
- Bravo! - Please say a few words.
很荣幸能跻身
Being part of these
国际精品酒店
international boutique hotels is a real honor.
我们为此付出了很长时间...
We've been working for a long time to achieve...
我女儿在哪
Where's my daughter?
索莱
Sole!
- 马丁 我们会找到她的...  - 放开我
- Martín, we'll find your daughter... - Get away from me!
马丁 冷静点...
Martin, please relax...
如果你们谁敢动我女儿一根头发
If one of you has touched a single hair on my daughter's head,
我一定会让你们不得好死
I swear I'll let you have it with both barrels.
马丁 拜托了
Martín, please.
- 索莱 索莱 - 把这个收好
- Sole! Sole! - Put this away.
我的女儿在哪啊 天呐
Where's my daughter? Please!
别拍了
Stop filming!
我的女儿啊... 帮帮我...
My daughter... Please...
我们会找到你女儿的 马丁
We'll find your daughter, Martín.
不要慌
Stay calm.
埃尔薇拉: 靠 朋友们 太吓人了吧!!!
纳乔： 他们一直在问我怎么回事
里奇: 不如就糊弄过去吧
反正我说实话也没人信
巴内: 哈哈哈哈哈
海梅: 玩什么该死的笔仙... 可怜的索莱
索莱: @&￥*&#…
海梅: 我靠!
纳乔: 什么鬼!!!
是你吗 索莱? 你
是你吗 索莱? 你在
是你吗 索莱? 你在哪
是你吗 索莱? 你在哪儿
是你吗 索莱? 你在哪儿?
巴内: 是你吗 索莱? 你在哪儿?
?????
索 莱
索莱来电
索莱
Sole?
是你吗
Is that you?
你们得再请一次笔仙
You have to do the Ouija again.
这是唯一能让我回来的办法
It's the only way to bring me back.
我不知道该跟谁说
I didn't know who to tell about it.
你朋友能确定电话里的人就是她吗
But is your friend sure that it was her talking on the phone?
我不知道 她说自己跟她不太熟
I don't know, she said that she didn't really understand her,
可是还能是谁呢
but who else could it have been?
可能是有人想吓你们
Well, someone who wanted to scare you.
今晚 他们会再做一次
They're going to do it again, tonight.
- 做什么 - 请笔仙
- Do what? - The Ouija.
不行 你必须阻止他们
No. You have to stop them.
巴内说是索莱让她做的
Vane says that Sole asked her to do it.
这是唯一能救回她的办法
That it's the only way she can come back.
他们要去哪儿 墓地吗
Where are they going to do it? In the cemetery?
不 他们不想让任何人发现
No, they don't want anyone to see them.
他们要去荒宅
They're going to the abandoned house.
那里有几间地下室
There are some cellars underneath.
该死 我不该告诉你的
Fuck. I shouldn't have told you.
这件事我谁都不说
This is between you and me.
- 你能保证吗 - 我保证
- Do you promise? - I promise.
我很害怕
I'm scared.
不会有事的
Nothing's going to happen.
他们在这儿吗
Are they here?
从这进去就是地下室了
If you go in through here you get to the cellars.
很有意思 你看看就知道了
It's really cool, you'll see.
听着 你们不能这么做
Guys, you have to stop this right now.
你朋友吗 埃尔薇拉 还找个朋友来 你真行
That's your friend, Elvira? A friend? Fucking great.
你是巴内吗
Are you Vane?
你应该把手机交给警方
What you have to do is take
让他们追踪电话来源
that phone to the police to trace the call.
我看过通话记录了 什么都没有
I looked at the list of calls and it isn't there.
没关系 警方肯定知道该怎么处理
It doesn't matter, I'm sure the police know how to do it.
索莱跟她说
Sole told her that we had
我们必须这么做  我们就得这么做
to do this and that's what we're going to do.
如果出事了怎么办
And what if something happens?
如果又有人消失了怎么办
What if we try it and one of us disappears?
该死 有东西
Fuck, that's really something.
现...
Do...
在...
it...
现在...
Do it...
现在开始
Do it now.
是你吗 索莱
Is that you, Sole?
是
Yes
太吓人了
Fuck, that's scary.
我们能怎么帮你
How can we help you?
他们...
They...
想...
want...
他们想跟你说话
They want to talk to you.
谁 他们想跟谁说话
Who? Who do they want to talk to?
不
No.
不 我不做
No. I won't.
埃尔薇拉 告诉你朋友
Elvira, tell your friend
要么按照笔仙说的做
that either she does what the Ouija tells her
要么就让她滚出去
or she gets the fuck out of here.
埃莱娜... 你应该这么做
Elena... I think you should do it.
为了索莱
For Sole.
我不知道你为什么这么害怕
I don't know why you're so scared,
我妈都那么说你了
after what my mother says about you.
你妈妈说什么
And what does your mother say?
你丈夫离开是因为你疯了
That your husband left because you're crazy.
你能看见鬼怪之类的
You see ghosts and things like that.
把...
Give...
银币...
us...
给...
the...
- 我们 - 把银币给我们
- Coin. - Give us the coin.
什么银币
What coin?
- 该死 老兄 - 怎么回事
- Holy fucking shit, dude! - What's going on?
又来了 该死
Not again! Fuck me!
索莱...
Sole...
索莱... 非常感谢
Sole... Thank you very much.
马丁 你应该谢谢埃莱娜
You should thank Elena, Martín.
我们走
Let's go.
你跟她聊吧 我一点都不理解
You talk to her, because I don't understand any of this.
- 所以  - 所以什么
- Well? - Well, what?
你看到了 是不是
You saw it, didn't you?
- 我什么都没看到 - 但你就在那
- I didn't see anything. - But you were right there!
帕科 我说我没看见 就是没看见
Paco, if I say I didn't see it, I didn't see it.
我在玩笔仙 抬起头她就在那了
I was with the Ouija, I looked up and there she was.
事情就是这样 你也理解 我情绪不好
That's how it happened. As you can understand, I'm very upset.
- 但她肯定说了什么 - 她没开口
- But she must have said something. - She didn't open her mouth.
她说想向神父忏悔
Well, she said she wants to confess to the priest.
- 我没听到 - 埃莱娜 她是和我说的
- I didn't hear that. - Elena, she said it to me.
我们都有点紧张
We're all a bit tense, I think.
我不用向任何人解释
I don't have to give any explanations to anybody.
就算我和孩子们玩了笔仙
If I was with the kids doing the Ouija,
也是因为他们要我去的
it's because they wanted me there.
没人问你这些 埃莱娜 你能冷静点吗
No one has asked you anything, Elena. Will you just calm down?
不 我知道事情会怎么样
No, I know how this works.
明天 所有人都会说
Tomorrow everyone is going to
是我带走了那个女孩 都是我的错
say that I took the girl, that it's all my fault,
是我诱导他们
and that I was the one who
玩笔仙招魂的
put the idea of a séance into their heads.
放松 现在的重点是你帮忙找到了她
Relax. Right now, all that matters is that you helped find her.
我们不知道怎么回事
We don't know how,
但她就在那 和她父亲在一起
but there she is, with her father.
亲爱的
Yes, love.
- 放松 - 不 我还要在这待一段时间
- Relax, please. - No, no, I'll be here for a while yet.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
充满恩典的万福玛利亚
Hail Mary full of grace.
假设无罪
Conceived without sin.
你母亲的事 我很遗憾
I'm very sorry about your mother.
发生了那样的灾祸 我们都会感到内疚...
When a misfortune like that happens, we all feel guilty...
但是我想让你知道
But I want you to know
你妈妈全心全意爱着你
that your mother loved you with all her heart,
发生的一切都不是你的错
and that none of what happened is your fault.
我不是来谈我母亲的事的
I haven't come to talk about my mother.
我来这不是因为我想来
I'm not here because I want to be.
什么
What?
他们让我跟你谈谈
They told me to talk to you.
- 谁跟你说的 - 你的朋友们
- Who told you that? - Your friends.
我不知道你说的是谁
I don't know who you're talking about.
他们想让我告诉你些事
They wanted me to tell you something.
什么事
What is it?
把我们的东西还回来
愿你的天国降临
...thy kingdom come.
愿你的旨意行在地上 如同行在天上
Thy will be done on Earth as it is in Heaven.
我很抱歉
I'm really sorry.
为什么 孩子
Why, child?
因为你今晚要死了
Because you're going to die tonight.
早上吃一粒
Take one in the morning.
- 写下来... - 救命 救命
- Write it down so... - Please! Please!
救命...
Please...
先生 先坐下
Please, sir, sit here.
- 我的心脏... - 你吃什么药
- It's my heart... - What are you taking?
- 我觉得是卡托普利 - 拿点过来
- I think it's Captopril. - Get some.
卡托普利: 用于治疗高血压和某些类型的充血性心力衰竭
- 我觉得是卡托普利 - 拿点过来
- I think it's Captopril. - Get some.
- 一百毫克 可能是心脏病发作了 - 好
- 100 mg. I think it's a heart attack. - Okay.
人们都吓坏了 曼努埃尔
People are terrified, Manuel.
这是两个月里的第二起死亡事件
It's the second death in two months.
- 人们一直都很害怕 - 见鬼
- People are always terrified. - For fuck's sake.
那个女孩说他要死了
The girl tells him he's
一个小时后 他真的死了
going to die and an hour later the man's dead.
谁都会被吓到
It's enough to scare anybody.
如果你心脏不好 有人在街上拦住你
If you have a dicky heart and someone stops you in the street
告诉你 你要死了
to tell you that you're going to die,
这肯定没什么好处
let's say that it doesn't exactly help.
她和她父亲在那
There she is with her father.
那个女孩跟你说了什么
What did the girl say when you talked to her?
忏悔要保密
Secret of confession.
- 她告诉你了吗 - 什么
- Did she tell you about this? - What?
她用做这种事威胁过你吗
Did she threaten you with doing things like this?
- 你和埃莱娜聊过吗 - 没有
- Have you talked to Elena? - No.
好吧 聊过 我们必须做点什么
Well, yes. We'll have to do something.
我们要跟所有人解释
We have to explain to everyone
那只是一场灾祸而已
that this was a misfortune, nothing more.
那个男人心脏不好 也没吃药
The man had a bad heart, he hadn't taken his medication,
这就是神秘事件的真相
and that's the end of the mystery. Fuck!
他们怎么敢来这里
How can they have the nerve to turn up here!
埃尔薇拉: 我不怕你
明天再谈
该死 所有人都说我着魔了
Fuck, everyone says I'm possessed.
别理他们
Ignore them.
- 他们是一群乡巴佬 - 不 他们说的对
- They're all a bunch of hicks. - No, they're right.
我遇到的事很不正常
What's happening to me isn't normal.
你遇到了什么事
But what's happening to you?
- 自从我在那里... - 那里 哪里
- Since I was there... - There, where?
我不知道 在另一边
I don't know, on the other side.
就像... 一场梦 但又是真实的
It was like... A dream, but for real.
我回来后就能看到奇怪的东西
Well, it's like since I was there I see really weird things.
怎么奇怪
Weird how?
人们...
People...
人们都变得不一样了 他们...
People aren't the same, they have like...
被颜色围着
colors around them.
什么
What?
就像... 有东西环绕着你
Yes, it's like... something that surrounds you.
你现在是蓝色的
Yours is blue right now, okay?
不用担心 是好事
Don't worry, that's good.
死的那个男人有红色的边界 都快变成黑色了
The man who died had a red border, it was almost black.
你能看见所有人的颜色吗
And do you see that with everyone?
看到那些人了吗
You see those people?
都是蓝的
All blue.
孩子们的几乎是白色的
There are some that are almost white, the children.
但是 那边 远处的 看到他了吗
But on the other hand, there, in the distance, you see him?
谁
Who?
拿着花的那个男人
The man carrying flowers.
看到了 他怎么了
Yes. What about him?
这表多少钱
How much are the watches?
埃尔薇拉
Elvira.
你还好吗 亲爱的
How are you, sweetheart?
别紧张 怎么了 为什么约在这见面
Calm down. What's wrong? Why are we meeting here?
是索莱... 她吓到我了
It's Sole... She's scaring me.
这是什么意思
What do you mean?
跟我来
Follow me.
- 看里面的那个人 - 谁
- Look at the man in there. - Who?
和店员说话的那个
The one being served now.
他怎么了
What about him?
索莱说他就快死了
Sole says he's going to die.
- 你确定 确定是那个人 - 我确定
- Are you sure? Precisely that man? - Yes.
她能看到他周围围绕着一些什么东西
She sees something that he's got around him.
- 光晕 - 是的
- An aura. - Yes!
有些好 有些坏 那个人的看起来...
Some are good, and others are bad. And it seems that man...
- 她什么时候说的 - 就在刚刚 在她家
- But when did she tell you that? - Just now, in her house.
我一直跟着他 所以我才给你打电话
I've been following him, that's why I rang you.
那你想怎么办
And what do you want us to do?
我不知道 或许我们应该告诉他
I don't know, maybe we should say something to him.
不 不 那太疯狂了
No, no. That's crazy.
- 他要走了 我们怎么办 - 什么都别做
- He's leaving. What should we do? - Nothing.
- 你好 - 什么事
- Hey! - Yes?
没什么 抱歉
Nothing. I'm sorry.
没事的
It's okay.
什么都不会发生
Nothing is going to happen.
好吗
Okay?
出什么事了
What's happened?
好了 埃尔薇拉 慢慢呼吸
Come on, Elvira, breathe slowly.
就这样  现在呼气
That's it. Now let it go...
我叫住了他
I stopped him.
我本来想要警告他 但他继续走了
I was going to warn him, but he kept on walking.
这不是谁的错 不怪你 不怪索莱 不怪我
No one is to blame. Not you, not Sole, not me,
也不怪那个男人 这只是场意外
not the man in the overcoat. This was an accident.
你不知道会发生的才叫意外
An accident is when you don't know what's going to happen,
但是我们知道
and we knew.
她知道
She knew.
为什么
Why?
冷静点 非常好
Calm down, very well.
我只能告诉她这一切都只是巧合
So I have to tell her that it's all sheer coincidence,
- 但这不是真的 - 当然是真的
- and it isn't true! - Of course it's true.
你说那个人分心了
You said the man was distracted,
他走到那条路的时候在看你们
looking at you when he stepped into the road.
你是说是我们造成的意外吗
We caused it! Is that what you're saying?
听着 埃莱娜 你这么想毫无益处
Look, Elena, that way of thinking won't do any good.
你要我怎么想
How do you want me to think?
一切快要失控了 又一次失控
This is getting out of control. Again.
唯一能够帮助我们的人
The only one who can help
正在无视这一切
us understand any of it is ignoring it all.
我和他谈过了 他说"忏悔要保密"
I spoke to him. He says that it's a "Secret of confession".
镇上的人一定都吓坏了
The town must be freaking out.
他们可能觉得那个女孩是巫师什么的
They probably think that girl is a witch or something.
你真的觉得我们什么都不用做吗
Are you really telling me we're not going to do anything?
让我想想能做什么
I'll see what I can think of.
- 来 慢一点 - 小心 加把劲 上来
- Come on. Slowly. - Be careful. Come on, hop on.
小心
Be careful.
她又把你牵扯进去了
She's getting you involved again.
梅尔切 大家都很恐慌 我必须帮忙
Merche, people are scared. I have to help.
- 我不介意 - 好吧 你不介意
- I don't mind. - Oh, you don't mind.
- 你还很享受吧 - 不是那样的
- You're enjoying it. - It isn't that.
那是怎样 我看就是那样
Then what is it? All I see is that
那个女人想方设法要把你扯进来
that woman doesn't know what to invent to get involved with you.
发生了什么
What's happened here?
一个女孩失踪了 她去和那个女孩的朋友们招魂
A girl disappears and she goes and has a séance with her friends.
有人死了 她又在现场 事情一团糟
People die and there she is, stirring things up.
这还不够 现在她还想要你帮她
But that isn't enough, now she wants you to help her.
- 你有没有在听我说话 - 我在听
- Are you listening to me? - I'm listening.
你要承担责任还要维护声誉
You have responsibilities, a reputation to maintain.
这样对市政厅影响不好 对生意也不好
is isn't good for the town hall, and even less for business.
让别人去做 你要置身事外
Let others do it. You keep out of it.
索莱 亲爱的 开下门
Sole, love, open the door please.
曼努埃尔神父来了 他来见你了
Father Manuel is here, he's come to see you.
索莱 和他聊一聊 会对你有帮助
Sole! Talk to him. It'll help you.
索莱 我是贝尔加拉神父 开下门
Sole, I'm Father Vergara. Open the door.
索莱
Sole!
她没有呼吸了
She isn't breathing.
- 索莱 索莱 - 她没有呼吸了
- Sole! Sole! - She isn't breathing!
索莱 就这样
Sole? That's right.
没事了 放松 放松 放松
You're all right. Take it easy. Take it easy. Take it easy.
- 好了... - 你没事吧 宝贝
- Now... - Are you all right, sweetheart?
你没有按照他们说的去做
You didn't do what they asked.
你为什么不做 神父 他们现在来怪我了
Why didn't you do it, Father? Now they're blaming me.
她有些神志不清
She's delirious.
是红色的 快要黑了
It's red, almost black.
光晕 我的吗
The aura? Is it me?
不 是他的
No, it's him.
就在今天 今晚
It's going to be today, tonight.
一切都结束了 结束了
It's over. It's over.
深呼吸 深呼吸 一切都结束了
Breathe. Breathe. It's over.
我说过让你别牵扯进去
I told you not to get involved,
你不听 你直接一头扎进去
but no! You dive right in, head first.
那个女孩想上吊自杀
The girl tried to hang herself,
梅尔切 如果我们没去...
Merche. If we hadn't been there...
我都不敢去想
I can't bear to think about it.
- 这个镇子到底怎么了 - 我不知道
- What's going on in this town? - I don't know.
而且这还不是最糟的
And that isn't the worst.
索莱说神父会是下一个
Sole told the priest that he'd be next.
- 她真的这么说了 - 是她说的
- She really said that? - Those were her words.
那他怎么说
And what did he say?
他什么都没说就走了
Nothing, he went silent and he left.
我们得让他离开
We have to get rid of him.
- 什么 - 他不能留在镇里 帕科
- What? - He can't stay in this town, Paco.
你看看大家 再看看你自己
Look at how everyone is! Look at how you are!
他可是神父 又不是镇书记
He's the priest, it isn't like he's the town clerk.
我连镇书记也不能辞退
And I can't even fire the town clerk...
- 去塞戈维亚和主教说 - 我和他说什么
- Go to Segovia and talk to the bishop. - And what do I tell him?
事实 自从他到这里
The truth, that since he got here,
我们都不好过以至于夜不能寐
we're so upset we haven't been able to sleep.
- 就这么简单 - 这都是他的错吗
- As simple as that. - And it's all his fault?
当然是
Fuck, it's obvious.
好吧 向我证明 假设我是主教 你要怎么说
Look, prove it. I'm the bishop, you come in and what do you say?
就像那样 自从那个人出现
Just that. That since that man appeared,
我们的生活充满了不幸
we've had nothing but misfortunes.
非常好 你知道他会怎么回答吗
Very well. Do you know what his answer will be?
我的话都是胡扯 而我是个笨蛋
That my argument is shit, and that I'm a dickhead.
嘿 别这样和我说话
Hey, don't talk to me like that.
你想控告某人要有证据 没有证据不如不说
When you accuse someone, you need proof. If not, you keep quiet.
说那个人和怪事有关
Saying that this man has
牛犊 失踪的女孩
something to do with the calf, the missing girl,
还有抱花男人的死
the death of the man with the flowers,
这是欲加之罪
is talking for the sake of talking.
他进过监狱 没有人通知过我们
He was in prison and no one told us anything.
我们有权要求一个正常的神父 对吗
In this town we have a right to have a normal priest. Yes or no?
如果那个女孩是对的怎么办
And what if the girl is right?
明天他就死了
And tomorrow he's dead?
我主耶稣基督 我为对你不敬深感悔悟
Lord Jesus Christ, I am heartily sorry for having offended you.
我决心不再违戒律
I resolve never to sin again,
行苦修 以赎罪告解
to confess and to carry out my penance.
主 我将自己交与你手 求你宽恕我的罪
I offer you, Lord, my life, in satisfaction for all my sins
你必以圣洁的血液 热情与死亡
and in this way I trust that you will forgive me,
宽恕我的罪过
through the merits of your blood, passion and death.
如果...天亮前...你不...把银币...还给我们
If before... daybreak... you don't... give us back... the coin...
我们就...毁掉...这个镇...和你最爱的...人
we will destroy... that town... and the people... you love most.
你父亲知道你在这吗
Does your father know you're here?
进来吧
Come inside.
想喝点什么
Would you like anything?
水 谢谢
Water. Thanks.
明天学校有课吗
Have you got school tomorrow?
不
No.
我在赛普尔韦达读高中
I go to the high school, in Sepúlveda.
我父亲载我去
My father takes me.
你最应该做的事情
That's the best thing you can do,
就是专注在学业上 把这些都忘掉
concentrate on your studies, and forget all this.
回到正轨能帮助你理清思绪
Routine helps you to sort out your ideas.
他们让我把这个给你
They told me to give you this.
是给你的
It's for you.
他们说 如果这个还不够
They say that, if this isn't enough,
我会继续切下我的手指和耳朵 或者我的舌头
I'm to continue cutting off my fingers and ears, or my tongue,
直到你交出他们想要的东西
until you give them what they're looking for.
警察局吗 是警察局吗
Police? Police?
我在塞戈维亚的佩德拉萨镇
I'm calling from the town of Pedraza, in Segovia.
不 很紧急 是的
No! It's urgent! Yes.
听得到吗
Can you hear me?
是的
Yes!
听得到吗
Can you hear me?
你敢和警察说
If you speak to them,
我就告诉他们 这是你干的
I'm going to tell them that you did it.
不 住手 住手
No! Stop! Stop!
冷静点
Take it easy.
我们一起去找银币吧
Shall we go and look for the coin?
看到这些他们一定很满意
They're going to be very happy.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
我在想事情 仅此而已
I was thinking, that's all.
想什么呢
About what?
我愈发确定了
I'm more and more certain about it.
确定什么
More and more certain...?
你应该跟我走
That you should come with me.
我现在实在没心情谈这个
My mind is in no shape for talking about that now.
但现在不想就来不及了
But it's exactly now that you have to think about it.
你需要换个环境
You need a change of scenery,
你必须离开这个鬼地方 不然你会被逼疯的
you need to get out of this foul hole that's driving you crazy.
为什么所有男人最后都说我疯了
Why do all men end up calling me crazy?
我是说 你告诉我的这一切
What I mean is that all this you're telling me
关于笔仙的事情 那个女孩...
about the Ouija, about that girl...
怎么说呢 你陷得太深了
I don't know, you're getting too involved,
你设身处地地为她着想
you make such an effort to put yourself in her place
结果自己落得和她一样的下场
that you end up in her place,
开始相信那些东西是真的 但它们不是
believing that those things are real, and they're not real.
一旦你离开这里 你就不会这么想了
As soon as you get away from here, you'll see it all differently.
这是肯定的
That's for sure.
你家里有人吗
Hey, is there someone in your house?
没有啊
No.
那为什么灯亮着
Then you left the lights on.
抱歉 你不在家 我就从后门进来了
Sorry. You weren't here. I came in the back door.
抱歉 我不得不来
Sorry, I had to get in.
你在干什么 马上出去
What are you doing? Get out now!
听着 你告诉那姑娘银币的事了吗
Listen. Did you tell the girl about the coin?
- 什么 - 你告诉索莱 或者她朋友了吗
- What? - Sole, or any of her friends.
你没听到她说的吗
Didn't you hear her?
埃莱娜说你得离开了
Elena says that you're to leave,
你不走的话 我就把你赶出去了
and if you don't I'll throw you out.
埃尔薇拉来过这里
Elvira was here.
她一定是看到了所有东西 然后告诉索莱了
She must have seen all this and told Sole.
肯定是这样
There's no other explanation.
索莱 亲爱的 你怎么了
Sole, honey. What happened to you?
- 是他干的 - 不是这样
- It was him. - It isn't true.
你个狗娘养的
You son of a bitch!
索莱 亲爱的 一切都会没事的 不许动
Sole, love, everything will be okay. Don't you move!
我们去医院 你一定会没事的
We'll go the hospital. Everything will be all right.
不
No.
罗克
Roque!
- 你在做什么 - 罗克
- What are you doing? - Roque!
你找到银币了吗
Have you found it?
什么都别告诉她
Don't tell her a thing.
- 在我这里 - 把它给我
- I've got it. - Give it to me.
- 你要它做什么 - 闭嘴 埃莱娜
- What do you want it for? - Elena, shut up.
这样我就不会看到那些奇怪的东西了
So that they'll get out of my head.
你也能看到那些东西
Have you seen them too?
他们就在这里
They're here.
他们答应你什么了
What did they promise you?
让你妈妈复活 对吧
It's your mother, isn't it?
你妈妈已经死了 索莱
Your mother is dead, Sole,
没有人能让她起死复生 他们也没有这个能力
no one will be able to bring her back, not even them.
你妈妈是因为得了不治之症
Your mother took her own
自己结束了自己的生命
life because she had an incurable disease.
和你没有任何关系
It has nothing to do with you.
她很爱你 所以她不忍心让你看到她遭受痛苦
She loved you, and she couldn't bear for you to see her suffer.
- 这不是你的错 - 你和他们都一样
- It's not your fault. - You're like them.
你也不过是想利用我
You want to use me too.
是的 我和他们一样 我也想利用你
Yes! I'm like them, I want to use you.
因为你就是个吓坏了的 愚蠢的小屁孩
Because you're just a stupid adolescent who's scared to death!
敢和我们所有人作对
Dare to stand up to all of us!
管住你的思维 别受他们控制
Close your mind, don't let anyone in.
只有你可以做到
You're the only one who can do it!
所有人都给我闭嘴 住口
Shut up, all of you! Stop!
别控制我
Get out of my head!
够了 住口
Enough! Stop!
罗克...
Roque...
想想你妈妈
Think of your mother!
想想你妈妈 索莱
Think of your mother, Sole!
他们就无计可施了
They can't fight against that.
不
No!
想想你妈妈
Think of your mother!
罗克...
Roque...
- 索莱怎么样了 - 还好
- How's Sole? - Fine.
现在医生技术都很好
They do these things very well now,
但那个疤恐怕是一辈子消不掉了
but that scar will be there forever.
和你的一样 你还好吗
Like yours. I mean, how are you?
我没什么的
Mine is nothing.
刀刺在了一根肋骨上 没有刺穿肺
The knife hit against a rib and so it didn't pierce his lung.
总的来说我很幸运了
All things considered, I was lucky.
- 马丁呢 他怎么样 - 他在外面
- And Martín? How is he? - Outside.
他们给他服了太多药 他有些混乱
They've given him so many pills he doesn't even know where he is.
告诉他 什么都不用担心
Tell him that, as far as I'm concerned, he needn't worry.
我不会提起诉讼的
I'm not going to press charges.
你不打算告诉我 到底发生什么了吗
Aren't you going to say what happened?
我也不知道发生了什么
I don't know what happened.
她闯进来 把刀刺向我
She came in, she stuck the
别的我什么都不记得了
knife in me and I can't remember anything else.
他们的烦心事已经够多了 你说呢
They've got enough problems, don't you think?
那我就...
Well... I'm going to...
好好休息 罗克
Thanks, Roque.
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
你和贝尔加拉谈过了吗
Have you spoken to Vergara?
谈过了 他跟我说了一些
Yes, he told me his version of the facts.
我来猜猜看
I imagine it was:
我和孩子们提过银币的事情
That I talked to the kids about the coin,
- 索莱很执着... - 是的
- Sole got obsessed with it... - Yes.
她母亲的死对她的影响很大
And she was very affected by her mother's death,
她自残 是为了惩罚自己
and she harmed herself, to punish herself for it.
差不多就是这样
More or less, yes.
我猜你的描述
I imagine that your version
应该不太一致吧
doesn't exactly fit with his, does it?
没人在乎我的说法
No one cares about my version.
我在乎
I do.
你妻子说得对 整个镇子都靠你安慰
Your wife is right: You're the shoulder the whole town cries on.
别管她了 你有什么都可以和我说
Forget about that now. You know you can talk to me.
- 究竟怎么回事 - 他闯进我家找...
- What happened? - He got in my house to find...
银币
The coin?
他打破了后门上的玻璃
He broke the glass in the garden door,
搜遍了整栋房子
he searched the whole house.
然后发生了一些事情... 我也解释不了
And then things happened. Things that... I can't explain.
- 我能想象 - 你想象不到 没有人能想到
- I can imagine. - You can't imagine! Nobody can!
我宁可他把银币拿走 我不想留它在家里
I only wish he had taken it. I don't want it in my house.
我应该听罗克的 离开这个小镇
I should listen to Roque and get out of this town.
- 在彻底疯掉前逃离 - 我不想让你走
- Escape, before I go completely crazy. - I don't want you to go.
拜托了...
Please...
这事绝不会到此为止 肯定还会有事情发生
This isn't going to end here, more things are going to happen.
我没有勇气 一个人去面对这一切
I don't have the courage to cope with this on my own.
那你也离开吧
You leave too.
不行 我的一切都在这里
I can't. My life is here,
有太多的东西 我不能放弃
there are too many things that I can't give up.
太多的责任
Too many responsibilities.
不要离开
Don't leave.
如果有人应该离开 也不该是你和我
Besides, if anyone must leave this town, it's neither you nor me.
告诉他 别担心
Tell him not to worry.
告诉主教大人无需担心
Tell his eminence he's not to worry.
我会照顾好他 等待您的到来
I'll take care of him, until you come.
等待合适的时机
Until the right time comes.
犹大的时刻
Judas's time.